watch4beauty.com 2019-03-31

# Legal - WATCH4BEAUTY | Nude Art Magazine

LEGAL 

Thanks for taking the time to learn about W4B's legal policies. It's important stuff. If you have any questions about these policies, please [contact us](mailto:support@watch4beauty.com "support@watch4beauty.com"). We comply with the GDPR.

## Terms and Conditions

These Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") govern your relationship with watch4beauty.com website (the "Service") operated by K Production s.r.o. ("us", "we", or "our").

Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using the Service.

Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.

By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.

### Subscriptions

Some parts of the Service are billed on a subscription basis ("Subscription(s)"). You will be billed in advance on a recurring and periodic basis ("Billing Cycle"). Billing cycles are set either on a monthly or annual basis, depending on the type of subscription plan you select when purchasing a Subscription.

Subscriptions are operated by our authorized sales agents CCBill and Epoch. Please visit ccbill.com and epoch.com.

At the end of each Billing Cycle, your Subscription will automatically renew under the exact same conditions unless you cancel it or K Production s.r.o. cancels it. You may cancel your Subscription renewal either through CCBill or Epoch account management page or by contacting K Production s.r.o. customer support team.

A valid payment method, including credit card or PayPal, is required to process the payment for your Subscription. You shall provide our authorized sales agents with accurate and complete billing information including full name, address, state, zip code, telephone number, and a valid payment method information. By submitting such payment information, you automatically authorize our sales agents to charge all Subscription fees incurred through your account to any such payment instruments. K Production s.r.o. have no access to your payment details.

### Free Trial

K Production s.r.o. may, at its sole discretion, offer a Subscription with a free trial for a limited period of time ("Free Trial").

You may be required to enter your billing information in order to sign up for the Free Trial.

If you do enter your billing information when signing up for the Free Trial, you will not be charged by our authorized sales agents until the Free Trial has expired. On the last day of the Free Trial period, unless you cancelled your Subscription, you will be automatically charged the applicable Subscription fees for the type of Subscription you have selected.

At any time and without notice, K Production s.r.o. reserves the right to (i) modify the terms and conditions of the Free Trial offer, or (ii) cancel such Free Trial offer.

### Fee Changes

K Production s.r.o., in its sole discretion and at any time, may modify the Subscription fees for the Subscriptions. Any Subscription fee change will become effective at the end of the then-current Billing Cycle.

K Production s.r.o. will provide you with a reasonable prior notice of any change in Subscription fees to give you an opportunity to terminate your Subscription before such change becomes effective.

Your continued use of the Service after the Subscription fee change comes into effect constitutes your agreement to pay the modified Subscription fee amount.

### Refunds

Certain refund requests for Subscriptions may be considered by K Production s.r.o. on a case-by-case basis and granted in sole discretion of K Production s.r.o..

### Accounts

When you create an account with us, you must provide us information that is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your account on our Service.

You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Service and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service.

You agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.

You may not use as a username the name of another person or entity or that is not lawfully available for use, a name or trade mark that is subject to any rights of another person or entity other than you without appropriate authorization, or a name that is otherwise offensive, vulgar or obscene.

### Intellectual Property

W4B® is a registered trademark of K Production s.r.o..

The Service and its original content, features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of K Production s.r.o. and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the Czech Republic and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of K Production s.r.o..

All photographs and videos included in this website are strictly for non-commercial use. Reproduction without permission is strictly prohibited.

### Links To Other Web Sites

Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by K Production s.r.o..

K Production s.r.o. has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that K Production s.r.o. shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.

We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.

### Termination

We may terminate or suspend your account immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.

Upon termination, your right to use the Service will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service.

### Limitation Of Liability

In no event shall K Production s.r.o., nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.

### Disclaimer

Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.

K Production s.r.o. its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.

### Governing Law

These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Czech Republic, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.

### Changes

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.

By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.

Effective date 2018.1.31

## Privacy Policy

K Production s.r.o. ("us", "we", or "our") operates the watch4beauty.com website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from watch4beauty.com

We comply with the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

### Definitions

#### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

#### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

#### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

#### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

#### Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

#### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

#### User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. Types of Data Collected:

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address

  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.

  * Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.

  * Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

### Use of Data

K Production s.r.o. uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service

  * To notify you about changes to our Service

  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so

  * To provide customer support

  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service

  * To monitor the usage of our Service

  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues

  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Retention of Data

K Production s.r.o. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

K Production s.r.o. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Czech Republic and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Czech Republic and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

K Production s.r.o. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure Of Data

K Production s.r.o. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation

  * To protect and defend the rights or property of K Production s.r.o.

  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service

  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public

  * To protect against legal liability

### Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### "Do Not Track" Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Rights

K Production s.r.o. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you

  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate

  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to K Production s.r.o.. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

Google Analytics

  * Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/...](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

#### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

CCBill

  * Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.ccbill.com/...](https://www.ccbill.com/policies.php)

Epoch

  * Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://epoch.com/...](https://epoch.com/privacy.html)

### Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Effective date 2018.1.31

## Cookies Policy

K Production s.r.o. ("us", "we", or "our") uses cookies on the watch4beauty.com website (the "Service"). By using the Service, you consent to the use of cookies.

Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Service, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.

### What are cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text sent to your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you.

Cookies can be "persistent" or "session" cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when you go offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.

### How K Production s.r.o. uses cookies

When you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

  * To enable certain functions of the Service

  * To provide analytics

  * To store your preferences

We use both session and persistent cookies on the Service and we use different types of cookies to run the Service:

  * Essential cookies. We may use essential cookies to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts.

  * Preferences cookies. We may use preferences cookies to remember information that changes the way the Service behaves or looks, such as the "remember me" functionality of a registered user or a user's language preference.

  * Analytics cookies. We may use analytics cookies to track information how the Service is used so that we can make improvements. We may also use analytics cookies to test new advertisements, pages, features or new functionality of the Service to see how our users react to them.

### Third-party cookies

In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service, deliver advertisements on and through the Service, and so on.

### What are your choices regarding cookies

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.

  * For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google: [https://support.google.com/...](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050)

  * For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft: [http://support.microsoft.com/...](http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835)

  * For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla: [https://support.mozilla.org/...](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored)

  * For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple: [https://support.apple.com/...](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_US)

  * For any other web browser, please visit your web browser's official web pages.

### Where can you find more information about cookies

You can learn more about cookies and the following third-party websites:

  * AllAboutCookies: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

  * Network Advertising Initiative: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

Effective date 2018.1.31

## Mail Policy

K Production s.r.o. ("us", "we", or "our") operates the watch4beauty.com website (the "Service").

This statement informs you of our policies regarding the collection and use of email address when you use our Service.

We take our Mail Policy very seriously. We know that problems with spam are very serious and we want to take any precaution to send only solicited mail.

### Collecting and Communications

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address.

We may use your email address to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

### Sending Emails

We promise the following:

  * We will never use third party services to send our newsletters, we will do it on our own.

  * We will never give or sell email addresses of our subscribers to anyone.

  * We will never send anything other than our newsletters or special announcements (once a week).

  * We will protect all email addresses gathered to not let them leak.

We are taking these precautions of responsible bulk mail sender for easy identification of our bulk mails and quick response to misuse:

  * Campaign headers X-Campaign-ID

  * Bulk identification headers Precedence: Bulk

  * VERP headers (variable envelope return path) for bounce processing

  * Active sender policy framework (SPF) setup

  * Registered response addresses for abuse reports at the Network Abuse Clearinghouse

  * Working and responsive support at support@watch4beauty.com

Effective date 2018.1.31

## 18 U.S.C. §2257

In compliance with the US Federal Labeling and Record-Keeping Law (also known as 18 U.S.C. §2257 Record Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement), all models, actors, actresses and other persons that appear in any visual depiction of actual sexually explicit conduct appearing or otherwise contained in this website were over the age of eighteen years at the time of the creation of such depictions. All model's proof of age is held by the Custodian of Records, which is listed below. All content and images are in full compliance with the requirements of 18 U.S.C. §2257 and associated regulations.

All records required to comply with the Record keeping requirements pursuant to 18 U.S.C. §2257 are kept by Custodian of Records Martin Kinkal, and are available for inspection during normal business hours at the following address: K Production s.r.o., Tusarova 55, 170 00 Prague 7, Czech Republic.

Effective date 2018.1.31
